family-vacation-getaways-at-los-angeles-theme-parks.com 2010-12-27

# Privacy Policy

### Here is the Privacy Policy of www.Family-Vacation-Getaways-at-Los-Angeles-Theme-Parks.com

**Your privacy is important!** This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use www.Family-Vacation-Getaways-at-Los-Angeles-Theme-Parks.com (AKA www.Family-Vacation-Getaways.com), as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

Family-Vacation-Getaways.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website. 

**Personal Information:** www.Family-Vacation-Getaways.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number. 

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest, sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries. 

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties. 

**Use of Cookies:** We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. (For example, cookies are used to help distinguish the number of repeat visitors to a page versus the number of total visits made to a page.) Currently this website does not allow for personalizing pages (you can't make a page say, "Welcome Back, Jane Doe!" for example.) However, this feature may be added in the future, in which case, a cookie would enable www.Family-Vacation-Getaways.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. If you follow any links away from this website (via either advertisements or checking out other websites recommended "for further information") the website to which you head will probably use cookies, as well.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site if they are added. See the bottom of this page for information about how to clear cookies from your computer.

 **Use of cookies by advertisers and other websites:** This website uses third party advertising and makes referrals to other websites that we think are interesting. Advertisers and other interesting websites may collect and save any personal information you give them. Be sure to read through the privacy policy of any website you reach via advertising or other links on www.Family-Vacation-Getaways.com.

Even if you do not give out your name (or other personal information) to websites you reach from links on www.Family-Vacation-Getaways.com, any advertiser's website (or informational website) may use cookies that can tell which pages you've visited on their websites. Sometimes, advertisers may use this information about your visits to their websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For example, you will see many ads by Google on this website; to see how they use cookies to provide you with ads that suit your interests, you may view the following [information about Google's privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

 **Children's Online Privacy Protection Act:** This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

**Non-Personal Information:** In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

**Release of Information:** If www.Family-Vacation-Getaways.com is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us. There are currently no plans to sell or otherwise transfer this website.

 **How You Can Correct or Remove Information:** We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please use the Contact Us page. 

**Updates and Effective Date:** Family-Vacation-Getaways.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it. 

**Agreeing to Terms:** If you do not agree to www.Family-Vacation-Getaway.com's Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site. 

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy. Thank you.

 **How to clear your browser's cache and/or cookies:** If you would like to clear your computer's cache or remove cookies after visiting this website (or the websites to which we link for the purpose of giving you further information about a topic) then you may use the following instructions:

How to clear cache:

1.) For Internet Explorer 6-- From the top menu choose the following options: Tools > Internet Options > General tabClick 'Delete Files' button and OK.

2.) For Internet Explorer 7-- From the top menu choose the following options: Tools > Internet Options > General tab; Click 'Delete...' button from Browsing History; Click 'Delete Files...'; Click 'Ok'

3.) For Firefox-- From the top menu choose the following options:Tools > Options > Privacy > Cache tab; Click 'Clear Cache Now' and OK.

4.) For Opera-- From the top menu choose the following options: Tools > Preferences > Advanced > History > Disc cache; Click 'Empty now' and OK.

5.) For Netscape-- From the top menu choose the following options: Tools > Options > Privacy > Cache; Click 'Clear Cache' and OK.

 **How do I clear cookies in my browser?**

1.) For Internet Explorer-- From the top menu choose the following options: Tools > Internet Options > General tab; Click 'Delete Cookies' button and OK.

2.) For Firefox-- From the top menu choose the following options: Tools > Options > Privacy > Cookies tab; Click 'Clear Cookies Now' and OK.

3.) For Opera-- From the top menu choose the following options: Tools > Options > Privacy > Cookies; Click 'Manage cookies' and click 'Delete' on the selected cookies and OK.

4.) For Netscape-- From the top menu choose the following options: Tools > Options > Privacy > Cookies; Click 'Clear' and OK.

**Share this page:  **| | | |   
---|---|---|---|---  
| | |   
  
Enjoy this page? Please pay it forward. Here's how...
